
  {
    "levelName": "Lists",
    "index": "5",
    "puzzles": [
      {
        "testCases": [
          {
            "problem": "[1, 2, 3]",
            "answer": "1"
          },
          {
            "problem": "[\"apple\", \"banana\", \"cherry\"]",
            "answer": "apple"
          }
        ],
        "hiddenTestCases": [
          {
            "problem": "[4,5,6]",
            "answer": "4"
          }
        ],
        "startingCode": "PuzzleInfo/OneStartingCode.txt",
        "directions": "PuzzleInfo/OneDirections.txt",
        "puzzleName": "One",
        "puzzleIndex": "0"
      },
      {
        "testCases": [
          {
            "problem": "[1, 2, 3], 2",
            "answer": "True"
          },
          {
            "problem": "[\"apple\", \"banana\", \"cherry\"], \"grape\"",
            "answer": "False"
          }
        ],
        "hiddenTestCases": [
          {
            "problem": "[5,6,7], 6",
            "answer": "True"
          },
          {
            "problem": "[5,6,7], 8",
            "answer": "False"
          }
        ],
        "startingCode": "PuzzleInfo/TwoStartingCode.txt",
        "directions": "PuzzleInfo/TwoDirections.txt",
        "puzzleName": "Two",
        "puzzleIndex": "1"
      },
      {
        "testCases": [
          {
            "problem": "[1, 2, 3]",
            "answer": "[3, 2, 1]"
          },
          {
            "problem": "[\"apple\", \"banana\", \"cherry\"]",
            "answer": "['cherry', 'banana', 'apple']"
          }
        ],
        "hiddenTestCases": [
          {
            "problem": "[5, 6 ,7]",
            "answer": "[7, 6, 5]"
          },
          {
            "problem": "[8, 9]",
            "answer": "[9, 8]"
          }
        ],
        "startingCode": "PuzzleInfo/ThreeStartingCode.txt",
        "directions": "PuzzleInfo/ThreeDirections.txt",
        "puzzleName": "Three",
        "puzzleIndex": "2"
      },
      {
        "testCases": [
          {
            "problem": "[1, 2], [3, 4]",
            "answer": "[1, 2, 3, 4]"
          },
          {
            "problem": "[\"apple\", \"banana\"], [\"cherry\", \"date\"]",
            "answer": "['apple', 'banana', 'cherry', 'date']"
          }
        ],
        "hiddenTestCases": [
          {
            "problem": "[3, 4], [1, 2]",
            "answer": "[3, 4, 1, 2]"
          }
        ],
        "startingCode": "PuzzleInfo/FourStartingCode.txt",
        "directions": "PuzzleInfo/FourDirections.txt",
        "puzzleName": "Four",
        "puzzleIndex": "3"
      },
      {
        "testCases": [
          {
            "problem": "[1, 2, 3], 1",
            "answer": "2"
          },
          {
            "problem": "[\"apple\", \"banana\", \"cherry\"], 2",
            "answer": "cherry"
          }
        ],
        "hiddenTestCases": [
          {
            "problem": "[1, 2, 3], 2",
            "answer": "3"
          }
        ],
        "startingCode": "PuzzleInfo/FiveStartingCode.txt",
        "directions": "PuzzleInfo/FiveDirections.txt",
        "puzzleName": "Five",
        "puzzleIndex": "4"
      }
    ]
  }